identified.com 2016-06-04

# Workday Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Statement

Data privacy is important to the Workday Group, which includes Workday, Inc. and its affiliates (“Workday”). This Privacy Statement describes the personal information we collect about you as a visitor to our websites such as [www.workday.com](http://www.workday.com/), [community.workday.com](http://community.workday.com/), or other Workday websites that link to this Privacy Statement, how we use it, with whom we share it, and describes your choices regarding certain types of processing. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, contact [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com) or see the “Contact Us” section later in this statement.

By visiting our websites or providing us with your personal information, you consent to the collection, processing, and storage of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.

##### Information Collected

Workday collects, processes, and retains information about you when you visit our websites. You may choose to provide us with information, such as your name, email address, company information, street address, telephone number, or other information, to access protected information on our websites or so we can follow up with you after your visit. If you choose to participate in the Workday Community, you may choose to provide us with additional information such as a photo, social media profiles, areas of expertise, and other information. We may combine other publicly available information related to the organization from which you work for with the information that you provide to us. Workday or Workday service providers may observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as IP address) relating to your use of our websites and our services. We may also use log files, cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click on, and other actions you may take when accessing our websites, services, or emails. For more information about our use of these technologies and how to control them, see our Cookies and Similar Technologies section below. We may collect and store this information and combine this information with other personal information you may have provided.

##### Customer Data

As part of Workday's services, customers may load data into Workday servers. Workday will not share or distribute any such customer data except as provided in the contractual agreement between Workday and customer, or as may be required by law. [Please refer to the Workday Service Privacy Policy for more details](http://www.workday.com/company/service_privacy.php).

##### Use of Your Information

Workday uses the information we collect about you to:

  * Provide you with the Workday websites and any support you may request;
  * Respond to your inquiries or fulfill your requests;
  * Diagnose website technical problems;
  * Send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as product announcements, newsletters, educational materials, and upcoming events;
  * Send you administrative information such as notices related to product, service, or policy changes;
  * Understand how our websites and services are being used;
  * Personalize your experience on our websites and present products or features that are tailored to your interests;
  * Prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activity; and
  * As described to you when we collect the information.

##### Disclosure

Workday does not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information collected through its websites with third parties for their sole promotional purposes or as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Statement. Workday may share information with third party service providers contracted to provide services on our behalf. These third party service providers may only use information we provide to them as requested and instructed by Workday.

Workday may share information with third parties who resell the Workday service and/or provide value added services such as payroll outsourcing, tax filing, and other administrative services for our Mid-Market Channel offering. Workday’s Mid-Market Channel offering is designed to meet the needs of customers that have fewer than 1,500 employees.

Workday may offer solely or jointly with third parties, webinars, white paper downloads, or other services related to Workday offerings or services. We may share your contact information and product interest in these offering or services with third parties to communicate with you.

Workday may disclose information in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the website Terms and Conditions; or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

If Workday goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information collected through our website(s) may be among the assets transferred. A prominent notice will appear on our website(s) for 30 days after any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

##### Cookies and Similar Technologies

Cookies are small text files that our websites ask to place on your computer's hard drive. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We do not use cookies to read any other information on your computer's hard drive. We use cookie technology to authenticate your access to various areas of our websites, understand your interests, help analyze web traffic, and tailor content to your preferences. You can configure your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you disable cookies, some parts of our websites may not function properly or at all.

We use web beacons or transparent GIF files, that may be included on our websites and messages, that are typically used in conjunction with cookies, to help us manage our online advertising and measure its effectiveness, identify our users, and analyze traffic. Web beacons may also assist us with understanding which advertisements are most effective by notifying us if webpages, emails, or ads have been viewed or clicked. The information that we collect by means of these technologies is anonymous.

We may also use other technologies similar to cookies and web beacons such as HTML5 Local Storage, local shared objects, tags, and scripts. These technologies are used for similar purposes as cookies and web beacons. These technologies can operate across all of your browsers, and in some instances will require additional steps beyond browser settings to manage their use and removal. We, and our third party partners use these technologies to provide certain features on our website, to display advertising based on your web browsing activities, and/or to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing these technologies.

##### Do Not Track

Without a common industry or legal standard for interpreting Do Not Track (DNT) signals, Workday does not respond to browser DNT signals. We will continue to monitor further development of a DNT standard by the privacy community and industry.

##### Online Advertising

Some online advertising uses information collected about your web browsing behavior such as the pages you have visited or the searches you have made. This information may be used to display more relevant advertisements and content to you on the Workday website and non-Workday websites. This information may also be used to display Workday employment opportunities to you if, for example, you have visited our careers page. The information collected is linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising may come from Workday or through third party ad networks.

If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising on our websites, please click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/); if you are located in the European Union, please click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

##### Data Processing

Any personal information collected about EU visitors via our websites is processed in the United States by Workday or by a third party acting on our behalf. When you provide personal information to Workday, you consent to the processing of your information in the United States. Our websites are hosted in the United States.

##### Third-Party Websites

This website contains links to other sites that Workday does not own or control and whose privacy practices may differ from those of Workday. Please be aware that Workday is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our websites. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each website that collects personal information, as their privacy statement will govern any personal information you submit to those sites. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by Workday websites.

##### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our websites that may contain personal information such as the customer's name. We obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com).

##### Workday Community and Public Forums

On our websites, you may post comments or questions, for example on a blog, public forum, or Workday Community. Some of these features allow you to provide your personal information and create a profile. Personal information you submit in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. You should only post personal information to online forums with the awareness that the information will be made available to others inside and outside of Workday (unless stated otherwise). These comments and discussions are moderated, and may be accessed or deleted for technical or other reasons. Any comments posted by individuals on an online forum, such as Workday Community or blog, are his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of Workday. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

##### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our websites include social media features, such as YouTube videos, the Facebook Like button, and widgets such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our websites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

##### Security

Workday employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of information. However, the security of information transmitted through the Internet can never be guaranteed. Workday is not responsible for any interception or interruption of any communications through the Internet or for changes to or losses of information. Users of our sites are responsible for maintaining the security of any password, user ID, or other form of authentication involved in obtaining access to password protected or secure areas of any Workday websites. In order to protect you and your information, Workday may suspend your use of a website, without notice, pending an investigation, if any breach of security is suspected. Access to and use of password protected and/or secure area of any Workday site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized access to such areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution.

##### Opt-Out

If at any time after registering for information, your personal information changes or you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying updated information or your new choice. Simply send your request to [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com) or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Use the same email address if you do not wish to receive our newsletters, including the Workday newsletter.

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement or if you need to update, change or remove information, you can do so by contacting [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com) or by regular mail addressed to:

Workday, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
6230 Stoneridge Mall Road  
Pleasanton, CA 94588  
United States

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us via the information above. We will respond to your request to access or delete your information within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on this website and links to the Privacy Statement will indicate that the statement has been changed or updated. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement for any changes. For new users, changes or updates are effective upon posting. For existing users, changes or updates are effective 30 days after posting.

##### TRUSTe Privacy Program Statement

Workday has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Statement or practices, please contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). This TRUSTe certification covers only information that is collected through this website [www.workday.com](http://www.workday.com/) and the Workday Service, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website.

##### Safe Harbor Program Statement

Workday continues to comply with the U.S. – EU Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland, respectively. Workday has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity access, and enforcement. Information regarding the both the EU and Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks and Workday’s certification can be found at: [export.gov/safeharbor](http://export.gov/safeharbor).

To facilitate the transfer of personal information from the European Union and Switzerland, Workday relies upon other methods, such as standard contractual clauses, to meet the “adequacy requirements” under EU data protection laws.

##### APEC Program Statement

Workday’s privacy practices described in this Statement comply with the [APEC Cross Border Privacy Rules System](http://www.apec.org/Groups/Committee-on-Trade-and-Investment/~/media/Files/Groups/ECSG/CBPR/CBPR-PoliciesRulesGuidelines.ashx).

_Last Updated: May 3, 2016_
